<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<SPDXLicenseCollection xmlns="http://www.spdx.org/license">
    <exception licenseId="Google-WebRTC-additional-IP-rights"
               name="Google Additional IP Rights Grant (Patents) for WebRTC">
        <crossRefs>
            <crossRef>https://webrtc.googlesource.com/src/+/bb547203bfebcc478b263c4e9ca173c6fd5a0c5d/PATENTS</crossRef>
        </crossRefs>
        <text>
            <titleText>
                <p>Additional IP Rights Grant (Patents)</p>
            </titleText>

            <p>
                "This implementation" means the copyrightable works distributed by Google as part of <alt match=".+" name="project0">the WebRTC code package</alt>.
            </p>

            <p>
                Google hereby grants to you a perpetual, worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, irrevocable (except as stated in this section) patent license to make, have made, use, offer to sell, sell, import, transfer<optional>,</optional> and otherwise run, modify and propagate the contents of this implementation of <alt match=".+" name="project1">the WebRTC code package</alt>, where such license applies only to those patent claims, both currently owned by Google and acquired in the future, licensable by Google that are necessarily infringed by this implementation of <alt match=".+" name="project2">the WebRTC code package</alt>. This grant does not include claims that would be infringed only as a consequence of further modification of this implementation. If you or your agent or exclusive licensee institute or order or agree to the institution of patent litigation against any entity (including a cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging that this implementation of <alt match=".+" name="project3">the WebRTC code package</alt> or any code incorporated within this implementation of <alt match=".+" name="project4">the WebRTC code package</alt> constitutes direct or contributory patent infringement, or inducement of patent infringement, then any patent rights granted to you under this License for this implementation of <alt match=".+" name="project5">the WebRTC code package</alt> shall terminate as of the date such litigation is filed.
            </p>
        </text>
    </exception>
</SPDXLicenseCollection>
