<SPDX name="Apache License 1.1" identifier="Apache-1.1" osi-approved="true">
  <urls>
    <url>http://apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-1.1</url>
    <url>http://opensource.org/licenses/Apache-1.1</url>
  </urls>
  <notes>This license has been superseded by Apache License 2.0</notes>
  <license>
    <title>
      <p>Apache License 1.1</p>
    </title>
    <copyright>
      <p>Copyright (c) 2000 The Apache Software Foundation. All rights reserved.</p>
    </copyright>
    <body>
      <p>Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are permitted provided
         that the following conditions are met:</p>
      <list>
        <li>
          <b>1.</b>
          <p>Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions
             and the following disclaimer.</p>
        </li>
        <li>
          <b>2.</b>
          <p>Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of conditions
             and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the
             distribution.</p>
        </li>
        <li>
          <b>3.</b>
          <p>The end-user documentation included with the redistribution, if any, must include the following
             acknowledgment: 
            <br/>"This product includes software developed by 
            <alt name="organizationClause3" match=".+">the Apache Software Foundation (http://www.apache.org/)</alt>." 
            <br/>Alternately, this acknowledgment may appear in the software itself, if and wherever such
                 third-party acknowledgments normally appear. 
          </p>
        </li>
        <li>
          <b>4.</b>
          <p>The 
            <alt name="organizationClause4" match=".+">"Apache" and "Apache Software Foundation"</alt> must
            not be used to endorse or promote products derived from this software without prior written
            permission. For written permission, please contact 
            <alt name="contactClause4" match=".+">apache@apache.org</alt>
          </p>
        </li>
        <li>
          <b>5.</b>
          <p>Products derived from this software may not be called 
            <alt name="nameClause5" match=".+">"Apache" [ex. "Jakarta," "Apache," or "Apache Commons,"]</alt> nor may 
            <alt name="name2clause5" match=".+">"Apache" [ex. the names]</alt> appear in their name, without
            prior written permission of 
            <alt name="name3clause5" match=".+">the Apache Software Foundation</alt>. 
          </p>
        </li>
      </list>
      <p>THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED ''AS IS'' AND ANY EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED
         TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN
         NO EVENT SHALL 
        <alt name="copyrightHolderLiability" match=".+">THE APACHE SOFTWARE FOUNDATION OR ITS CONTRIBUTORS</alt>
        BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING,
        BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR
        BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT
        LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS
        SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE. 
      </p>
      <p>This software consists of voluntary contributions made by many individuals on behalf of the Apache
         Software Foundation. For more information on the Apache Software Foundation, please see
         http://www.apache.org/. Portions of this software are based upon public domain software originally
         written at the National Center for Supercomputing Applications, University of Illinois,
         Urbana-Champaign.</p>
    </body>
  </license>
</SPDX>