<SPDX name="BSD 2-clause &quot;Simplified&quot; License" identifier="BSD-2-Clause" osi-approved="true">
  <urls>
    <url>http://www.opensource.org/licenses/BSD-2-Clause</url>
  </urls>
  <license>
    <copyright>
      <p>Copyright (c) 
        <alt name="copyright" match=".+"> &lt;year&gt; &lt;owner&gt;</alt> All rights reserved. 
      </p>
    </copyright>
    <body>
      <p>Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are permitted provided
         that the following conditions are met:</p>
      <list>
        <li>
          <b>1.</b>
          <p>Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions
             and the following disclaimer.</p>
        </li>
        <li>
          <b>2.</b>
          <p>Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of conditions
             and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the
             distribution.</p>
        </li>
      </list>
      <p>THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY 
        <alt name="copyrightHolderAsIs" match=".+">THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS</alt> "AS IS" AND ANY
        EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY
        AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL 
        <alt name="copyrightHolderLiability" match=".+">THE COPYRIGHT HOLDER OR CONTRIBUTORS</alt> BE LIABLE FOR
        ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT
        LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS
        INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR
        TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF
        ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE. 
      </p>
    </body>
  </license>
</SPDX>