<SPDX name="BSD 2-clause NetBSD License" identifier="BSD-2-Clause-NetBSD" osi-approved="false">
  <urls>
    <url>http://www.netbsd.org/about/redistribution.html#default</url>
  </urls>
  <notes>NetBSD adopted this 2-clause license in 2008 for code contributed to NetBSD Foundation.</notes>
  <license>
    <copyright>
      <p>Copyright (c) 2008 The NetBSD Foundation, Inc. All rights reserved.</p>
    </copyright>
    <body>
      <p>This code is derived from software contributed to The NetBSD Foundation by 
        <alt name="contributors" match=".*"></alt>
      </p>
      <p>Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are permitted provided
         that the following conditions are met:</p>
      <list>
        <li>
          <b>1.</b>
          <p>Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions
             and the following disclaimer.</p>
        </li>
        <li>
          <b>2.</b>
          <p>Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of conditions
             and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the
             distribution.</p>
        </li>
      </list>
      <p>THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY 
        <alt name="copyrightHolderAsIs" match=".+">THE NETBSD FOUNDATION, INC. AND CONTRIBUTORS</alt> ``AS IS''
        AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF
        MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL 
        <alt name="copyrightHolderLiability" match=".+">THE FOUNDATION OR CONTRIBUTORS</alt> BE LIABLE FOR ANY
        DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED
        TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS
        INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR
        TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF
        ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE. 
      </p>
    </body>
  </license>
</SPDX>