<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<SPDXLicenseCollection xmlns="http://www.spdx.org/license">
   <license isOsiApproved="false" licenseId="FPA" name="Fairfield Programming Association General Code License">
      <crossRefs>
         <crossRef>https://about.fairfieldprogramming.org/licenses/code</crossRef>
      </crossRefs>
    <text>
      <titleText>
         <p>FPA General Code License</p>
      </titleText>
      <copyrightText>
         <p>Copyright (c) &lt;year&gt; &lt;copyright holders&gt;
         </p>
      </copyrightText>
      <p>Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal in the Software without limitation in the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, and/ or distribute copies of the Software in an educational or personal context, subject to the following conditions:</p>
      <list>
        <item>
          The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.
        </item>
      </list>
      <p>Permission is granted to sell and/ or distribute copies of the Software in a commercial context, subject to the following conditions:</p>
      <list>
        <item>
          Substantial changes: adding, removing, or modifying large parts, shall be developed in the Software. Reorganizing logic in the software does not warrant a substantial change.
        </item>
      </list>
      <p>THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT
         LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN
         NO EVENT SHALL <alt match=".+" name="copyrightHolder">THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS</alt> BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY,
         WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE
         SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.</p>
    </text>
  </license>
</SPDXLicenseCollection>
