<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<SPDXLicenseCollection xmlns="http://www.spdx.org/license">
   <license isOsiApproved="false" licenseId="HGL"
   name="HGL General License" listVersionAdded="">
      <crossRefs>
         <crossRef>https://evgnomon.org/hgl/</crossRef>
      </crossRefs>
      <standardLicenseHeader>
      </standardLicenseHeader>
      <notes>
      </notes>
      <text>
         <p>
            IN THE NAME OF FREEDOM HGL GENERAL LICENSE JULY
            2022 Copyright (C) 2022 evgnomon.org by Hamed
            Ghasemzadeh, ALL RIGHTS RESERVED hg@evgnomon.org
         </p>
         <p>
            IT IS NOT PROHIBITED TO COPY AND
            DISTRIBUTE VERBATIM COPIES OF THIS LICENSE.
         </p>
         <p>
            PREAMBLE We think license modification is not needed for those who
            want to use and/or improve our work which is why we put conditions
            on the way you can distribute a derivative work based on our work.
            We as an independent person receive your improvements under the same
            terms and conditions that you have received our work if you choose
            to distribute this work or a derivate work based on this work.
         </p>
         <p>
            This license, among other terms, does not prevent using our
            work in a closed source as long as no distribution takes
            place. The risk of being stuck in an obsolete work, that no
            one else contributes to, could be reduced by continuously
            trying to request useful contributions be taken back into
            this work under this license. Welcome to make a closed source
            work based on our work consistent with this license and
            welcome to contribute back to this work under this license.
         </p>
         <p>
            As we encourage you to use our work in a non-distributed closed
            source, we should protect ourselves against an alienated person
            who seeks dominance. First, we can always choose to have the upper
            hand by distributing to users which let us and our users improve
            forever without changing the license, and without getting divided.
            Second, our distribution can always be more affordable than those
            who don't distribute. These two let us eventually catch up. We
            protect ourselves for the moment that an alienated person can
            not stand anymore and the users get released towards our work.
            This license rules until that day, there and afterward forever.
         </p>
         <p>
            All rights are reserved for copyright holders to be able to
            protect the covered work for the purpose of this License.
         </p>
         <p>
            DEFINITIONS THE COVENANT the zero term of this agreement PERSON
            individual or legal entity RESTRICT to control something by law
            WORK what is protectable under copyright law MODIFY add to or
            delete from the work CODE a work represented by a particular
            arrangement or sequence of numbers, symbols, letters, words,
            on memory which is protectable under copyright SOURCE CODE
            a kind of code which is preferred for making modifications
            RECEIVE the situation that our work is transferred to a person
            in copy for use DEPENDENT owning more than fifty percent
            (50%) of the outstanding shares or beneficial ownership of the
            work performed by a person DISTRIBUTE the situation that an
            independent person receives our work for use COVERED WORK work
            which is covered under this License DERIVATIVE WORK work which is
            "derivative work" under copyright law based on the covered work
            0. Copying, modification and distribution of the covered work
            and derivative work based on the covered work is not restricted
            only if the following four conditions are all separately met:
         </p>
         <p>
            The source code of the distributed derivative work and thereby
            the distributed covered work is also distributed for all receivers
            of the distributed work. And a distributed derivative work based
            on the covered work is also licensed under this License without
            further term or condition or enforcing compliance by third parties
            including the state. And distribution of the covered work and a
            derivative work must keep the copyright notice and reference to
            this License. And * the following disclaimer appropriately published
            in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the
            distribution. 2. In order to have the covered work useful in a
            system with pieces under different licenses which are separately
            distributed consistent with the covenant, such a separately
            distributed work can exceptionally aggregate the covered work (or
            a derivative work based on the covered work) on the same medium
            without having the whole come into the scope of this License.
            The covered work or a derivative work based on the covered work
            can likewise aggregate a part which is separately distributed
            consistent with the covenant and under a different license
            without having the whole come into the scope of this license.
         </p>
         <p>
            EXCEPT WHEN OTHERWISE STATED IN WRITING, THE COPYRIGHT
            HOLDERS AND/OR OTHER PARTIES PROVIDE THE WORK "AS IS"
            WITHOUT IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR
            PURPOSE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY AND TITLE,
            AND ANY OTHER KIND OF EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES.
         </p>
         <p>
            IN NO EVENT SHALL ANY COPYRIGHT HOLDER, OR ANY OTHER PARTY WHO
            MAY MODIFY AND/OR REDISTRIBUTE THE PROGRAM AS PERMITTED ABOVE BE
            LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR
            CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT
            OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, LOSS OF GOODWILL,
            DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON
            ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY,
            OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY
            OUT OF THE USE OF THIS WORK OR AS A RESULT OF OUR LICENSE (OR THE
            AGREEMENT), EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
         </p>
         <p>
            However, You may at your option offer support, warranty,
            indemnity, or other liability obligations and/or rights
            consistent with this License in exchange for a fee.
         </p>
         <p>
            END OF TERMS AND CONDITIONS APPLICATION You apply
            this License on your work by referencing a verbatim
            copy of this License visible for receivers.
         </p>
         <p>
            Programs can print the copyright notice in the terminal like this:
         </p>
         <p>
            &lt; one line to give the program's name and a brief
            idea of what it does. &gt; Copyright (C) &lt;year(s)&gt;
            &lt;name of author&gt;. All rights reserved. License HGL:
            HGL General License &lt;http://evgnomon.org/hgl&gt; There
            is NO warranty express or implied; to the extent permitted
            by law. Source files under HGL contain this header:
         </p>
         <p>
            License-Identifier: HGL Copyright (C) &lt;year(s)&gt; &lt;name
            of author&gt;. All rights reserved. Copyright (C) &lt;year(s)&gt;
            &lt;name of author of the derivative work&gt;. All rights reserved.
         </p>
      </text>
   </license>
</SPDXLicenseCollection>
