<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<SPDXLicenseCollection xmlns="http://www.spdx.org/license">
   <license isOsiApproved="true" licenseId="MirOS" name="The MirOS Licence">
      <crossRefs>
         <crossRef>https://opensource.org/licenses/MirOS</crossRef>
      </crossRefs>
    <standardLicenseHeader>
      Copyright © <alt name="copyright" match=".+">year, year, year, …<br/>
           First M. Last &lt;user@host.domain&gt;</alt>
      <p>
	Provided that these terms and disclaimer and all copyright notices<br/>
	are retained or reproduced in an accompanying document, permission<br/>
	is granted to deal in this work without restriction, including un‐<br/>
	limited rights to use, publicly perform, distribute, sell, modify,<br/>
	merge, give away, or sublicence.</p>
      <p>
	This work is provided “AS IS” and WITHOUT WARRANTY of any kind, to<br/>
	the utmost extent permitted by applicable law, neither express nor<br/>
	implied; without malicious intent or gross negligence. In no event<br/>
	may a licensor, author or contributor be held liable for indirect,<br/>
	direct, other damage, loss, or other issues arising in any way out<br/>
	of dealing in the work, even if advised of the possibility of such<br/>
	damage or existence of a defect, except proven that it results out<br/>
	of said person’s immediate fault when using the work as intended.</p>
    </standardLicenseHeader>
    <text>
      <titleText>
         <p>The MirOS Licence</p>
      </titleText>
      <copyrightText>
         <p>Copyright [YEAR]
        <br/>[NAME] [EMAIL]
      </p>
      </copyrightText>

      <p>Provided that these terms and disclaimer and all copyright notices are retained or reproduced in an
         accompanying document, permission is granted to deal in this work without restriction, including
         unlimited rights to use, publicly perform, distribute, sell, modify, merge, give away, or
         sublicence.</p>
      <p>This work is provided "AS IS" and WITHOUT WARRANTY of any kind, to the utmost extent permitted by
         applicable law, neither express nor implied; without malicious intent or gross negligence. In no event
         may a licensor, author or contributor be held liable for indirect, direct, other damage, loss, or
         other issues arising in any way out of dealing in the work, even if advised of the possibility of such
         damage or existence of a defect, except proven that it results out of said person's immediate fault
         when using the work as intended.</p>

      <optional>
         <p>INSTRUCTIONS:
        <br/>To apply the template[1] specify the years of copyright (separated by comma, not as a range), the
             legal names of the copyright holders, and the real names of the authors (and licensors, possibly)
             if different. Avoid adding any text that could be read as further restriction.
      </p>
         <p>RATIONALE:
        <br/>This licence is apt for any kind of work (such as source code, fonts, documentation, graphics,
             sound etc.) and the preferred terms for work added to MirBSD. It has been drafted as
             universally usable equivalent of the "historic permission notice"[2] adapted to Europen law
             because some countries have specific requirements for disclaimers, and author and licensor can
             differ in (droit d'auteur) legislations. The licence conforms to DFSG[3] 1.1, OKD[4] 2.1,
             OSD[5] 1.9, CSD[6], qualifies as a Free Software[7] and Free Documentation[8] licence, for
             Free Cultural Works[9], and is thus included in relevant lists[10] of licences. It's also a
             licence suitable for OER and Open Content[18].
      </p>
         <p>The webpage[19] for this licence contains further information as well
         as additional resources such as translations.
      </p>
         <p>
        REFERENCES:
        <br/>
            <list>
               <item>
                  <bullet>[1]</bullet>
            also on the web with its own homepage[19] or as plaintext, either UTF-8 encoded at http://www.mirbsd.org/MirOS-Licence or with just ASCII at http://www.mirbsd.org/MirOS-Licence.asc
          </item>
               <item>
                  <bullet>[2]</bullet>
            https://opensource.org/licenses/historical.php
          </item>
               <item>
                  <bullet>[3]</bullet>
            http://www.debian.org/social_contract#guidelines
          </item>
               <item>
                  <bullet>[4]</bullet>
            http://opendefinition.org/od/2.1/en/
          </item>
               <item>
                  <bullet>[5]</bullet>
            https://opensource.org/osd
          </item>
               <item>
                  <bullet>[6]</bullet>
            http://copyfree.org/standard
          </item>
               <item>
                  <bullet>[7]</bullet>
            http://www.gnu.org/philosophy/free-sw.html
          </item>
               <item>
                  <bullet>[8]</bullet>
            http://www.gnu.org/philosophy/free-doc.html
          </item>
               <item>
                  <bullet>[9]</bullet>
            http://freedomdefined.org/Definition
          </item>
               <item>
                  <bullet>[10]</bullet>
            ifrOSS[11][12], Debian[13] (DFSG[3]), OKFN[14] (OKD[4]), OSI[15] (OSD[5]), Copyfree[16] (CSD[6]), although not yet on the FSF[17] list
          </item>
               <item>
                  <bullet>[11]</bullet>
            http://www.ifross.org/lizenz-center
          </item>
               <item>
                  <bullet>[12]</bullet>
            http://www.ifross.org/en/license-center
          </item>
               <item>
                  <bullet>[13]</bullet>
            https://wiki.debian.org/DFSGLicenses
          </item>
               <item>
                  <bullet>[14]</bullet>
            http://opendefinition.org/licenses/
          </item>
               <item>
                  <bullet>[15]</bullet>
            https://opensource.org/licenses/alphabetical
          </item>
               <item>
                  <bullet>[16]</bullet>
            http://copyfree.org/standard/licenses
          </item>
               <item>
                  <bullet>[17]</bullet>
            http://www.gnu.org/licenses/license-list.html
          </item>
               <item>
                  <bullet>[18]</bullet>
            http://opencontent.org/definition/
          </item>
               <item>
                  <bullet>[19]</bullet>
            http://www.mirbsd.org/MirOS-Licence.htm
          </item>
            </list>
         </p>
      </optional>
    </text>
  </license>
</SPDXLicenseCollection>
