<SPDX name="MirOS Licence" identifier="MirOS" osi-approved="true">
  <urls>
    <url>http://www.opensource.org/licenses/MirOS</url>
  </urls>
  <license>
    <title>
      <p>MirOS License</p>
    </title>
    <copyright>
      <p>Copyright [YEAR] 
        <br/>[NAME] [EMAIL] 
      </p>
    </copyright>
    <body>
      <p>Provided that these terms and disclaimer and all copyright notices are retained or reproduced in an
         accompanying document, permission is granted to deal in this work without restriction, including
         unlimited rights to use, publicly perform, distribute, sell, modify, merge, give away, or
         sublicence.</p>
      <p>This work is provided "AS IS" and WITHOUT WARRANTY of any kind, to the utmost extent permitted by
         applicable law, neither express nor implied; without malicious intent or gross negligence. In no event
         may a licensor, author or contributor be held liable for indirect, direct, other damage, loss, or
         other issues arising in any way out of dealing in the work, even if advised of the possibility of such
         damage or existence of a defect, except proven that it results out of said person's immediate fault
         when using the work as intended.</p>
    </body>
    <optional>
      <p>I_N_S_T_R_U_C_T_I_O_N_S_:_ 
        <br/>To apply the template(1) specify the years of copyright (separated by comma, not as a range), the
             legal names of the copyright holders, and the real names of the authors if different. Avoid
             adding text. 
      </p>
      <p>R_A_T_I_O_N_A_L_E_:_ 
        <br/>This licence is apt for any kind of work (such as source code, fonts, documentation, graphics,
             sound etc.) and the preferred terms for work added to MirBSD. It has been drafted as
             universally usable equivalent of the "historic permission notice"(2) adapted to Europen law
             because in some (droit d'auteur) countries authors cannot disclaim all liabi‐ lities.
             Compliance to DFSG(3) 1.1 is ensured, and GPLv2 compatibility is asserted unless advertising
             clauses are used. The MirOS Licence is certified to conform to OKD(4) 1.0 and OSD(5) 1.9, and
             qualifies as a Free Software(6) and also Free Documentation(7) licence and is included in some
             relevant lists(8)(9)(10). 
      </p>
      <p>We believe you are not liable for work inserted which is intellectual property of third parties, if you
         were not aware of the fact, act appropriately as soon as you become aware of that problem, seek an
         amicable solution for all parties, and never knowingly distribute a work without being authorised to
         do so by its licensors. 
        <br/>R_E_F_E_R_E_N_C_E_S_:_ 
      </p>
      <list>
        <li>
          <b>(1)</b>
          <p>also at http://mirbsd.de/MirOS-Licence</p>
        </li>
        <li>
          <b>(2)</b>
          <p>http://www.opensource.org/licenses/historical.php</p>
        </li>
        <li>
          <b>(3)</b>
          <p>http://www.debian.org/social_contract#guidelines</p>
        </li>
        <li>
          <b>(4)</b>
          <p>http://www.opendefinition.org/1.0</p>
        </li>
        <li>
          <b>(5)</b>
          <p>http://www.opensource.org/docs/osd</p>
        </li>
        <li>
          <b>(6)</b>
          <p>http://www.gnu.org/philosophy/free-sw.html</p>
        </li>
        <li>
          <b>(7)</b>
          <p>http://www.gnu.org/philosophy/free-doc.html</p>
        </li>
        <li>
          <b>(8)</b>
          <p>http://www.ifross.de/ifross_html/lizenzcenter.html</p>
        </li>
        <li>
          <b>(9)</b>
          <p>http://www.opendefinition.org/licenses</p>
        </li>
        <li>
          <b>(10)</b>
          <p>http://opensource.org/licenses/miros.html</p>
        </li>
      </list>
    </optional>
  </license>
</SPDX>