<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<SPDXLicenseCollection xmlns="http://www.spdx.org/license">
   <license licenseId="OTF2" name="OTF2 License Agreement" listVersionAdded="3.23">
      <crossRefs>
         <crossRef>https://perftools.pages.jsc.fz-juelich.de/cicd/otf2/tags/otf2-3.0/pdf/otf2.pdf</crossRef>
      </crossRefs>
      <text>
         <copyrightText>
          Copyright (c) 2009-2012, RWTH Aachen University, Germany<br />
          Copyright (c) 2009-2012, Gesellschaft fuer numerische Simulation mbH
                                   Braunschweig, Germany<br />
          Copyright (c) 2009-2021, Technische Universitaet Dresden, Germany<br />
          Copyright (c) 2009-2012, University of Oregon, Eugene, USA<br />
          Copyright (c) 2009-2021, Forschungszentrum Juelich GmbH, Germany<br />
          Copyright (c) 2009-2014, German Research School for Simulation Sciences GmbH,
                                   Juelich/Aachen, Germany<br />
          Copyright (c) 2009-2013, Technische Universitaet Muenchen, Germany<br />

          All rights reserved.
         </copyrightText>
         <p>
            Redistribution and use in source and binary
            forms, with or without modification, are permitted
            provided that the following conditions are met:
         </p>
         <list>
            <item>
               <bullet>1.</bullet>
               Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
               notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
            </item>
            <item>
               <bullet>2.</bullet>
               Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the
               above copyright notice, this list of conditions and
               the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or
               other materials provided with the distribution.
            </item>
            <item>
               <bullet>3.</bullet>
               Neither the names of<br />
                  RWTH Aachen University,<br />
                  Gesellschaft fuer numerische Simulation mbH Braunschweig,<br />
                  Technische Universitaet Dresden,<br />
                  University of Oregon, Eugene,<br />
                  Forschungszentrum Juelich GmbH,<br />
                  German Research School for Simulation Sciences GmbH, or the<br />
                  Technische Universitaet Muenchen,<br />
                 nor the names of their contributors may be used to endorse or promote
                 products derived from this software without specific prior written
                 permission.
            </item>
         </list>
         <p>
            THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS
            "AS IS" AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT
            LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR
            A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT
            OWNER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL,
            SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT
            LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE,
            DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY
            THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT
            (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE
            OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
         </p>
      </text>
   </license>
</SPDXLicenseCollection>
