<spdx name="Plexus Classworlds License" identifier="Plexus" osi-approved="false">
  <urls>
    <url>https://fedoraproject.org/wiki/Licensing/Plexus_Classworlds_License</url>
  </urls>
  <notes>dom4j uses this same license.</notes>
  <license>
    <copyright>
      <p>Copyright 
        <alt name="copyright" match=".+">2002 (C) The Codehaus</alt>. All Rights Reserved. 
      </p>
    </copyright>
    <body>
      <p>Redistribution and use of this software and associated documentation ("Software"), with or without
         modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:</p>
      <list>
        <li>
          <b>1.</b>
          <p>Redistributions of source code must retain copyright statements and notices. Redistributions must
             also contain a copy of this document.</p>
        </li>
        <li>
          <b>2.</b>
          <p>Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of conditions
             and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the
             distribution.</p>
        </li>
        <li>
          <b>3.</b>
          <p>The name 
            <alt name="nameClause3" match=".+">"classworlds”</alt> must not be used to endorse or promote
            products derived from this Software without prior written permission of 
            <alt name="organizationClause3" match=".+">The Codehaus</alt>. For written permission, please contact 
            <alt name="contactClause4" match=".+">bob@codehaus.org</alt>. 
          </p>
        </li>
        <li>
          <b>4.</b>
          <p>Products derived from this Software may not be called 
            <alt name="nameClause4" match=".+">"classworlds”</alt> nor may 
            <alt name="name2Clause4" match=".+">"classworlds”</alt> appear in their names without prior
            written permission of 
            <alt name="name3Clause4" match=".+">The Codehaus</alt>. 
            <alt name="trademark" match=".+">"classworlds”</alt> is a registered trademark of 
            <alt name="name4Clause4" match=".+">The Codehaus</alt>. 
          </p>
        </li>
        <li>
          <b>5.</b>
          <p>Due credit should be given to 
            <alt name="nameURL" match=".+">The Codehaus. (http://classworlds.codehaus.org/)</alt>. 
          </p>
        </li>
      </list>
      <p>THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY 
        <alt name="nameDisclaimer" match=".+">THE CODEHAUS</alt> AND CONTRIBUTORS ``AS IS'' AND ANY EXPRESSED OR
        IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS
        FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL 
        <alt name="name2Disclaimer" match=".+">THE CODEHAUS</alt> OR ITS CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT,
        INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO,
        PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION)
        HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING
        NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE
        POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE. 
      </p>
    </body>
  </license>
</spdx>
